Guide to the Department of Athletics, Yale University, Records Documenting Field Hockey
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Department of Athletics, Yale University, records documenting field hockey
1981-1997
RU 998
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.5
(1 box)
The records consist of a constitution, correspondence, reports, publications and topical files of the Department of Athletics documenting field hockey at Yale.
Yale University. Dept. of Athletics
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the Department of Athletics, 2005.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged alphabetically topic.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of a constitution, correspondence, reports, publications and topical files of the Department of Athletics documenting field hockey at Yale.
College athletes; College sports; Field hockey; Yale University -- Field hockey; Yale University -- Sports; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. Dept. of Athletics
- Records of the field hockey team, 1971-1997; Accession 2006-A-102
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until 2033
  - Articles and Constitution, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Budget, 1986, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1971-1989 (Box 1, Folder 3 - 6)
  - Foreign Tours -Holland, 1983, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - NCAA, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Reports, 1971, 1981-1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Results (W), 1986 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Stadium, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Summer Field Hockey Camp, 1985, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Training, 1983-1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Search -Head Coach Field Hockey and Lacrosse (W), 1980 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Publications, 1976-1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)